Guide to the Robert Creeley Computer Files, 1988-2002
Department of Special Collections
Creeley, Robert, Computer Files,
1988-2002
M1081
Creeley, Robert
.5 linear ft. (51 floppy disks, 5 Zip Disks, 3 CD-ROMs)
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Working papers and correspondence (principally outgoing but also incoming email) from the late 1980s through 2002.
Administrative Information
Access
All medical records for Robert Creeley and his family have been restricted, as have student recommendations and certain financial documents.
Electronic access to the Robert Creeley's Computer Files is currently being developed. Researcher's interested in accessing these materials should direct their requests to Michael Olson, Special Collections Assistant Librarian for Electronic Media Materials at (650) 723-1704 or mgolson@stanford.edu.
Acquisition Information
Purchased, 1999.
Biographical note
Recognized as a seminal figure of American letters in the second half of the 20th century, Robert White Creeley was born in Arlington, Massachusetts, on May 21, 1926, attended the Holderness School and then Harvard College. He received degrees from The Black Mountain College (B.A., 1956) and the University of New Mexico (M.A., 1960).
After serving as an ambulance driver for the American Field Service in India and Burma, then living for a year outside Aix-en-Provence, France, Creeley moved in 1952 to Mallorca, where he founded and edited the Divers Press. Upon his return to the United States and at the invitation of Charles Olson, Creeley moved to North Carolina where he joined the faculty of the Black Mountain College and edited the short-lived but highly influential journal, The Black Mountain Review (1954 -1957). Though he left the college in 1955, Creeley had already established himself as one of the leading figures of the literary avant-garde of the 1950s, establishing with Charles Olson the "Black Mountain School,"one of the most important movements in American letters, the foundation of Projective Verse, a break from the New Criticism and its "insistence on form as extrensic to the poem. He is notable for having established a lasting association with his literary mentors-Pound, Williams, Zukofsky, Bunting, and Dahlberg, among others-as well as those poets, writers and visual artists associated with the experimental arts of Black Mountain and the 1950s avant-garde. Among these are Paul Blackburn, John Chamberlain, Francisco Clemente, Cid Corman, Fielding Dawson, Jim Dine, Elsa Dorfman, Ed Dorn, Robert Duncan, Robert Indiana, R.B. Kitaj, Denise Levertov, Marisol, and especially Charles Olson, with whom Creeley corresponded extensively and collaborated on Mayan Letters (1953). Creeley was also a presence in the San Francisco poetry renaissance, where he formed a life-long association with Barth, Corso, Ginsberg, Kerouac, and McClure. Creeley is currently the SUNY Distinguished Professor of English and holds the Samuel P. Capen Chair of Poetry and Humanities at the State University of New York, Buffalo, a center of innovation and postmodern poetics, particularly that or those of the so-called "L-A-N-G-U-A-G-E" poets.
While his oeuvre includes short stories, essays, a novel, as well as criticism, Creeley is known principally as a poet. His friend and fellow poet John Ashbery has said of Creeley and his work, "He is the best we have." He has published over thirty volumes of verse since 1952, including: Words (1967); Pieces (1969); St. Martin's (1971); A Day Book (1972); Thirty Things (1974); Presences: A Text for Marisol (1976); Away (1976); Echoes (1982); Mirrors (1983); Memory Gardens (1986); and Windows (1990). His most recent collections of poems are Echoes (1994), published by New Directions, and Loops (1995), published by Nadja. Among his collections of poems are: For Love: Poems, 1950-1960 (1962); Poems 1950-1965 (1966); The Charm (1971); The Finger: Poems 1966-1969 (1970); The Door: Selected Poems (1975); Selected Poems (1976); The Collected Poems of Robert Creeley, 1945-1975 (1982); and Selected Poems 1945-1990 (1991).
Creeley has been awarded numerous literary prizes, including the Horst Bienek Lyrikpreis from the Bavarian Academy of Fine Arts, two Guggenheim Fellowships, a Fulbright Award, and a Rockefeller Grant. He was named New York State Poet Laureate in 1992. Creeley is a member of the American Academy of Arts and Letters.
He lives with his wife, Penelope Highton Creeley, and two of his six children in Buffalo, New York.
Biographical chronology
1926 Robert White Creeley born in Arlington, Massachusetts, May 21 to Oscar Slate and Genevieve Jules Creeley
1928 Left eye injured in accident
1930 Father died. Family moves to West Acton
1940 Entered Holderness School
1943 Entered Harvard College
1944-1945 Served in the American Field Service in India and Burma
1945 Returned to Harvard
1946 First published poem. Married Ann MacKinnon.
1947 Left Harvard without a degree
1948 Son David born
1948-1951 Lived in Littleton, NH where he bred pigeons
1950 Son Thomas born. Began correspondence with Charles Olson. Became American editor for Ranier Gerhardt's Fragmente
1951 Lived outside Aix-en-Province, France
1952 Daughter Charlotte born. Published Le Fou, his first book of poems. Moved to Majorca to establish Divers Press
1953 The Kind of Act of [poems] The Immoral Proposition [poems]
1954 The Gold Diggers [short stories] Taught at Black Mountain College First issue of Black Mountain Review, edited by Creeley, published in March
1955 Divorced from Ann MacKinnon All that is lovely in men [poems]
1956 Left Black Mountain College. If you [poems] Visited San Francisco Moves to Albuquerque Receives B.A. from Black Mountain College
1957 Married Bobbie Hall The Whip [collection of poems] Daughter Sarah born
1959 Daughter Katherine Williams born Moved to Guatemala A Form of Women [poems]
1960 Received M.A. from University of New Mexico Received Levinson Prize Included in The New American Peotry: 1945-1960
1961 Instructor at University of New Mexico
1962 For Love: Poems 1950-1960 Instructor at University of British Columbia
1963 Moved to Placitas, NM Vancouver Poetry Festival The Island [novel]
1964 Received Guggenheim Fellowship Received Oscar Blumenthal Prize
1965 Berkeley Poetry Conference The Gold Diggers and other stories [short stories] Edited with Donald Allen New American Story Words [poems] Received Rockefeller Grant
1966 National Educational Television Film, "Poetry: Robert Creeley"
1966-1970 Visiting Professor at State University of New York, Buffalo
1967 Words [poems] Edited with Donald Allen The New Writing in the USA Colloborated with R.B. Kitaj on A Sight Robert Creeley Reads [recorded reading]
1967-present Named Professor of English at SUNY, Buffalo
1968 Taught at University of New Mexico The Finger [poems] Numbers [poems]
1969 Pieces [poems] The Charm [poems]
1970 Moved to Bolinas, CA Taught at San Francisco State University A Quick Graph: Collected Notes & Essays [criticism]
1972 A Day Book [journal and poems] Listen [a radio play]
1973 Edited Whitman: Selected Poems Moved to Buffalo His Idea [poems]
1974 Thirty Things [poems]
1976 Presences: a text for Marisol [prose] Away [poems] Selected Poems Divorced Bobbie Hall Creeley
1977 Married Penelope Highton
1978 Boundary 2 published a double issue called Robert Creeley: A Gathering
1979 Later [poems]
1980 First volume of Charles Olson and Robert Creeley: The Complete Correspondence published by Black Sparrow Press
1981 Son William born Awarded Shelley Memorial Award from the Poetry Society of America
1982 NEA Grant
1983 Daughter Hannah born Hello: a journal [poems] DAAD Fellowship in Berlin
1984 Appointed David Gray Professor of Poetry and Letters, SUNY Buffalo
1985 Awarded Leone d'Oro Premio Speziale, Venice
1987 2nd DAAD Fellowship in Berlin Awarded Frost Medal by Poetry Society of America
1988 Robert Creeley's Life and Work published Received Distinguished Fulbright Award as Bicentennial Chair in American Studies, Helsinki University
1989-1991 New York State Poet
1990 Named Capen Professor of Poetry and Humanities, SUNY Buffalo
1991 Autobiography [essay]
1993 Tom Clark's Robert Creeley and the Genius of the American Common Place published Received Horst Bienek Lyrikpreis from Bavarian Academy of Fine Arts Tales out of School: Selected Interviews
1994 Echoes [poems]
1995 Loops: Ten Poems
Scope and Content
Robert Creeley's Computer Files document the life work of a leading American poet of the 20th century, one of the core members of the "Black Mountain School." They also document several important movements in American poetics in the second half of the century. The computer files include Creeley's personal and professional correspondence, journals, business records, personal mementos, games, and other documents generated and collected by him from 1988 to 1997.
Wherever Creeley's original arrangement of materials was encountered, his order has been respected. However, in many instances the computer files arrived without any clear indication of Creeley's own intellectual organization and disk numbers were assigned as the floppy disks were preserved. The disk numbers do not refer to the order in which the computer files were created and researcher's should reference the date ranges to determine correct chronological order.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
American literature--20th century.; Computer files.; Floppy disks.
Collection Contents
- Series 1. Floppy Disks, Robert Creeley's Computer Files contain a total of fifty-one 3 1/2 in. floppy disks. Of these thirty-nine floppy disks have so far been preserved and described in this series.
  - Zip Files, Email 31995 Apr 7 - 1996 May 7, M1081_S1_SS0_01_001_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 1)
    Disk contains five zipped email archives and one loose email message. Two of the zipped email archives (Email001.zip and Emailold.zip) are corrupt and unreadable. The remaining email archives primarily consist of Robert Creeley's incoming email from April 1995 through early May 1996.
    - Email000.zip, Corrupt email archive
      This Email archive is corrupt and currently unreadable.
    - Email001.zip1995 Apr 7 - 1995 Oct 3, 160 files, 316KB
      Zipped email archive primarily consisting of incoming email.
    - Email002.zip1995 Sept 11 - 1996 Feb 27, 136 Files, 343KB
    - Email004.zip1996 Mar 28 - 1996 May 7, 205 Files, 423KB
    - Emailold.zip, Corrupt email archive
    - Pktmp000.0011995 Sept 7, 1 File, 722 bytes
      Incoming email.
  - Email - Summer '96 fall '96 - Received, Sent1996 Summer - 1996 Fall, M1081_S1_SS0_01_002_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 2)
    - Email000.zip (Folder 1)
      This zipped email archive consists of pirmatily incoming correspondence.
    - Email001.zip (Folder 2)
    - In2.zip (Folder 3)
    - In3.zip (Folder 4)
    - In4.zip (Folder 5)
    - MailSnt1.zip (Folder 6)
    - Sent2.zip (Folder 7)
    - Sent3.zip (Folder 8)
    - Sent4.zip (Folder 9)
  - Email 21994 July 29 - 1994 Dec 10, M1081_S1_SS0_01_003_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 3)
    Diskette contains two zipped email archives of received correspondence.
    - Email000.zip1994 July 29 - 1994 Oct 20 (Folder 1)
    - Email0001.zip1994 Aug 22 - 1994 Dec 10 (Folder 2)
  - Chair Files Dec '911991 Apr 20 -1991 Nov 21, M1081_S1_SS0_01_004_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 4)
    Outgoing letters and faxes from Robert Creeley during his tenure as Chair of the Poetics Program at Univeristy of Buffalo / SUNY.
  - Chair 4 (94-95), M1081_S1_SS0_01_005_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 5)
    - Chair000.zip1993 Nov 24 - 1995 Feb 24, Zipped Archive (Folder 1)
    - Chair001.zip1994 Jan 5 - 1996 Feb 19, Zipped Archive (Folder 2)
    - Chair00A.zip1991 Sept 5 - 1994 Mar 12, Zipped Archive (Folder 3)
    - Chair00B.zip1994 Apr 19 - 1994 Nov 11, Zipped Archive (Folder 4)
    - Chair00C.zip1994 Sept 9 - 1995 May 17, Zipped Archive (Folder 5)
    - Pktmp000.rpt1995 Jan 18 (Folder 6)
  - Letters.zip 3, M1081_S1_SS0_01_006_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 6)
    - Letters1.zip1994 Apr 12 - 1995 Apr 7 (Folder 1)
    - Letters2.zip1995 May 21 - 1996 Feb 17 (Folder 2)
    - Letters3.zip1995 Nov 20 - 1996 Mar 28 (Folder 3)
  - Email 4 96, M1081_S1_SS0_01_007_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 7)
    Diskette contains 2 folders titled BIZ and LETTERS along with 93 loose files.
    - Biz1996 Mar 19 - 1996 June 14 (Folder 1)
    - Letters1996 Feb 26 - 1996 June 17, Contains a zipped email archive and 35 loose files (Folder 2)
    - [Misc. files], Contains a zipped email archive and 35 loose files (Folder 3)
      Misc files not associated with an archive or file folder.
  - Email 5 Spring '961995 Nov 8 - 1996 Mar 26, M1081_S1_SS0_01_008_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk. (Folder 8)
    1 zipped email archive and 1 loose file.
    - Email000.zip1995 Nov 8 - 1996 Mar 26 (Folder 1)
    - Pktmp000.A061995 Nov 8 (Folder 2)
  - This zip disk is described in Series 2 as Disk 09., Zip Disk (PC) (Folder 09)
  - This zip disk is described in Series 2 as Disk 10., Zip Disk (PC) (Folder 10)
  - Ligeia: MS Drafts Etc., M1081_S1_SS0_01_011_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 11)
    - Ligcol.11992 Aug 2 (Folder 1)
    - Ligeia.col1992 July 26 (Folder 2)
    - Ligeia.nte1992 July 26 (Folder 3)
    - Ligeia.pf11992 Aug 29 (Folder 4)
    - Ligeia.poe1991 Nov 25 (Folder 5)
    - Ligeia.pom1992 July 30 (Folder 6)
      Ligeia poem.
    - Ligeia.tit1992 July 30 (Folder 7)
      Ligeia title page.
    - Ligeia.wkg1992 July 18 (Folder 8)
    - Ligeia.wms1992 July 30 (Folder 9)
    - Ligeia01.rev1992 Aug 2 (Folder 10)
    - Ligeia02.rev1993 Apr 28 (Folder 11)
    - Ligeia1.wms1992 July 18 (Folder 12)
    - Ligeia1.wrk1992 July 19 (Folder 13)
    - Ligeia21992 Aug 2 (Folder 14)
    - Ligeia2.wkg1992 July 30 (Folder 15)
    - Ligeiaa.wkg1992 July 20 (Folder 17)
    - Ligeia2.wms1992 July 19 (Folder 16)
  - Faxes Sent/Received Summer '96 - 1, M1081_S1_SS0_01_012_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC). (Folder 12)
    Access to this floppy disk is restricted.
  - Faxes Sent/Received Summer '96 - 21996 July 1 - 1996 Aug 8, M1081_S1_SS0_01_013_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC). Diskette contains 21 FXD and FXR fax files. (Folder 13)
    Diskette contains sent and recieved faxes.
  - FL Fonts See Readme.txt1991 May, M1081_S1_SS0_01_014_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 14)
    Diskette contains font files.
  - Creeley Zipped Files 3/3, M1081_S1_SS0_01_015_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 15)
    Diskette contains two zipped archives.
    - Fax000.zip, 1 zipped archive (Folder 1)
      Zipped archive of receieved faxes. Page images are either corrupt or are unreadible by Quickview Plus emulation software.
    - Zip.zip1994 Jan 27 - 1994 Mar 2, 1 zipped archive (Folder 2)
      Zipped archive contains sent and received email.
  - Creeley Zipped Files 2/3, M1081_S1_SS0_01_016_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 16)
    Diskette contains eleven zipped archives.
    - Add2.zip1992 Oct 29 - 1994 Dec 16, 1 zipped archive (Folder 1)
    - Zizaca.zip1994 Oct 5 - 1994 Dec 16, 1 zipped archive (Folder 2)
      Outgoing email.
    - Chair001.zip1991 Sept 5 - 1994 Mar 12, 1 zipped archive (Folder 3)
      Outgoing emails and faxes.
    - Chair00B.zip1994 May 13 - 1994 Nov 23, 1 zipped archive (Folder 4)
    - Fulbrite.zip1994 July 21 - 1995 May 19, 1 zipped archive (Folder 5)
      Received and sent emails.
    - 1 zipped archive (Folder 6)
      Access to this zipped archive is restricted.
    - 1 zipped archive (Folder 7)
    - Letters1.zip1993 Dec 20 - 1994 Aug 2, 1 zipped archive (Folder 8)
      Outgoing email correspondence.
    - Poetry.zip1993 Feb 12 - 1994 Apr 23, 1 zipped archive (Folder 9)
      Poetry zip contains 3 zipped archives of poetry labeled 'out', 'uncollec', and 'pub'.
    - Pub.zip1992 Feb 1 - 1994 Oct 20, 1 zipped archive (Folder 10)
      Contains four additional zipped archives labeled 'out', 'pend', 'prose', and 'poetry'.
    - 1 zipped archive (Folder 11)
  - Biz 12, M1081_S1_SS0_01_017_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 17)
  - Biz 11, M1081_S1_SS0_01_018_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 18)
  - Biz 6 Following Biz 91B, M1081_S1_SS0_01_019_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 19)
  - Biz IV, M1081_S1_SS0_01_020_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 20)
  - A: Biz III, M1081_S1_SS0_01_021_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 21)
  - A: Biz II (including TEACH (88/89)), "Schedule [88/89]"1988 - 1989, M1081_S1_SS0_01_022_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 22)
  - A: Biz (Storage) I, M1081_S1_SS0_01_023_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 23)
  - A: Biz. 91B, M1081_S1_SS0_01_024_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 24)
  - Creeley Zipped Files 1/3, 5/98, M1081_S1_SS0_01_025_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 25)
    Diskette contains 8 compressed folders.
    - Biz.zip (Folder 1)
    - Biz89.zip (Folder 2)
    - Files91.zip (Folder 3)
    - Letters.zip (Folder 4)
    - Letters8.zip (Folder 5)
    - Prose (Folder 6)
    - Prose89.zip (Folder 7)
    - Uncollec.zip (Folder 8)
  - Zip Files 1C to be added to direct[ory?] etc): 1. Psitools. 2. CDR(ROM)220.zip. 3. Prose (for Mex. essay). 4. Schedule. 5. [?] (1995). 6. Hurricane (Game), M1081_S1_SS0_01_026_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 26)
    - CDR220.zip1990 - 1992 (Folder 1)
      Zipped Program files for installing CD-ROM.
    - Home.zip1989 Dec - 1995 Feb (Folder 2)
    - Hurr101.zip (Folder 3)
      Hurricane computer game.
    - Msav.rpt1997 Oct 31 (Folder 4)
      Microsoft Antivirus report.
    - Prosemex.zip1990 Nov - 1996 Oct (Folder 5)
      Bigraphical notes and prose pieces.
    - PS1TOOLS.zip1992 (Folder 6)
      Assorted software files.
    - Schedule.zip1994 - 1996 (Folder 7)
      Scedules from 1994-1996.
    - SIMP$$95.zip (Folder 8)
      Unknown data files possibly generated by anti-virus software.
  - zip files: NZ summer '95, Letters, Chair, Add, Fulbrite, Poetry, M1081_S1_SS0_01_027_OR; 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 27)
    Floppy disk contains orrespondence, faxes, and, Histoire de Florida
    - Add.zip1992 Dec 12 - 1995 May 20 (Folder 1)
      Zipped archive contains faxes, stationary templates and contact addresses.
    - Biz.zip1994 July 13 - 1995 May 17 (Folder 2)
    - Chair.zip1994 Nov 23 - 1995 May 17 (Folder 3)
      Correspondence relating to Robert Creeley's position as chair of the SUNY poetics program.
    - Fulbrite.zip1994 July 21 - 1995 May 19 (Folder 4)
      Correspondence relating to Robert Creeley's Fulbrite scholarship.
    - Letters.zip1994 May 13 - 1995 May 20 (Folder 5)
    - Poetry.zip1993 Feb 12 - 1995 Feb 28 (Folder 6)
      Zipped Archive contains complete and incomplete drafts of poetry.
  - Chops.zip, Add.zip, Poetry.zip, alex.zip, bookmark.zip, prose.zip, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 28)
    - Email (Folder 1)
      This uncompressed folder ontains two further sub-folders for incoming and sent email.
    - Add.zip1993 May 24 - 1996 June 19 (Folder 2)
      Zipped archive contains email addresses.
    - Alex.zip1995 Dec 29 - !995 Dec 30 (Folder 3)
      Draft of peom titled "Edges".
    - Avalenti.pen (Folder 4)
      Poem titled "A valentine for Pen".
    - Bookmark.zip1996 Apr 5 - 1996 June17 (Folder 5)
      Folder of five HTML documents containing Robert Creeley's bookmarks.
    - Chair.zip1995 Sept 20 - 1996 June 15 (Folder 6)
    - Chops.zip1996 Feb 1 - 1996 May 28 (Folder 7)
      Zipped Archive contains outgoing email.
    - Msav.rpt1997 Oct 31 (Folder 8)
      Micrsoft Antivirus reposrt.
    - Poetry.zip1993 Jan 28 - 1996 Mar 8 (Folder 9)
      Larged zipped archive containing poetry.
    - Prose.zip1994 Nov 11 - 1996 Nov 11 (Folder 10)
      Zipped Archive contains prose compositions.
    - Sumnfall.96 (Folder 11)
      Restricted File.
  - Biz96.zip, Chair.zip, chops.zip, email96.zip1995 Oct 20 - 1996 Dec 23, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 29)
    Diskette contains 6 zipped email archives.
    - Emailin1996 Mar 28 - 1996 Dec 23 (Folder 1)
      This folder contains two zipped archives of received email.
    - Emailsnt1996 July 7 - 1996 Dec 18 (Folder 2)
      This folder contains a single zipped archive of sentemail.
    - Biz96000.zip1995 Nov 2 - 1996 June 11 (Folder 3)
      Outgoing correspondence.
    - Chair000.zip1995 Oct 20 - 1996 May 24 (Folder 4)
      This archive contains outgoing correspondence.
    - Chops000.zip1995 Sept 14 - 1996 May 28 (Folder 5)
      Contains correspondence and fax cover letters.
    - Msav.rpt1997 Oct 31 (Folder 6)
  - Email 3 - 1997, Chops, Chair, Biz, Letters, Home 971996 May 20 - 1997 June 1, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 30)
    - Biz000.zip1996 Dec 9 - 1997 Jan 21 (Folder 1)
      outgoing corrrespondence and faxes.
    - Chair000.zip1996 Sept 2 - 1997 Mar 2 (Folder 2)
      Misc working documents and letters.
    - Chops000.zip1996 May 20 - 1996 Dec 19 (Folder 3)
      Corresondence and misc. poetry files
    - Emailin0.zip1996 June 18 - 1997 Mar 30 (Folder 4)
    - Restricted Archive (Folder 5)
    - Restricted File (Folder 6)
    - Letters0.zip1996 Sept 4 - 1996 Dec 6 (Folder 7)
    - Letters1.zip1997 Jan 3 - 1997 June 1 (Folder 8)
      Zipped archive containing primarily faxes.
    - Msav.rpt1997 Oct 31 (Folder 9)
    - Restricted File (Folder 10)
    - Pktmp000.rpt1997 Feb 5 (Folder 11)
      Report to Robert Grenier.
    - Restricted File (Folder 12)
      Access to this archive is restricted.
    - Scroggin.0001997 Dec 17 (Folder 13)
    - Sent000.zip (Folder 14)
      Sent Eamil folder.
  - Email zip 1 1997 (also faxes), 3 1/2" Floppy Disk. (Folder 31)
    Floppy Disk contains email correspondence and faxes
    - Emailadd.zip1993 May 4 - 1996 Sept 26 (Folder 1)
      Email addreesses.
    - Emailin.zip1997 Apr 2 - 1997 may 20 (Folder 2)
      Incoming email correspondence.
    - Emailin0.zip1997 Apr 2 - 1997 May 7 (Folder 3)
    - Emailsnt.zip1997 Mar 30 - 1997 May 14 (Folder 4)
    - Faxesin.zip1995 Sept 11 - 1996 June 19 (Folder 5)
      Unable to view these faxes using emulation software.
  - Email 1997 (2) zip1997, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 32)
    - AMPO1997 (Folder 1)
      A single folder containing 10 files and 1 zipped archive.
    - Email1997 (Folder 2)
      Single folder containing 3 zipped archives of email.
    - Msav.rpt1997 Oct 31 (Folder 3)
      Microsoft Antivirus Report.
  - Chops.zip '97, Bookmark zip, zukconf.zip, Poetry.zip, add.zip, Prose.zip1996 Sept 12 - 1997 June 12, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 33)
    - Biz.zip1997 Feb 2 - 1997 June 12 (Folder 1)
      Outgoing faxes and correspondence.
    - Bookmark.zip1996 Apr 20 - 1997 Apr 3 (Folder 2)
      Robert Creeley's browser bookmarkds.
    - Chair.zip1996 Sept 12 - 1997 June 7 (Folder 3)
    - Chops.zip1996 Nov 12 - 1997 June 3 (Folder 4)
      Miscellanious outgoing correspondence.
    - Msav.rpt1997 Oct 31 (Folder 5)
    - Poetry.zip1997 Mar 25 - 1997 June 5 (Folder 6)
      This zipped archive contains Robert Creeley poetry and cannot be opened using emulation software.
    - Poetryad.zip1997 Jan 17 - 1997 Feb 9 (Folder 7)
      Zipped archive containing Robert Creeley Poetry. This archive cannot be viewed using emulation softare.
    - Prose.zip1997 Jan 22 - 1997 June 11 (Folder 8)
      Zipped archive contains micellanious prose work.
    - Zukconf.zip1997 Mar 28 - 1997 May 13 (Folder 9)
      Working files related to the Louis Zukofsky Conference held at the University at Buffalo, SUNY.
  - Letters 11988 July 11 - 1992 Feb 24, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 34)
    Floppy disk contains personal correspondence.
    - Letters1.zip1988 July 11 - 1989 June 22 (Folder 1)
      Personal Correspondeece.
    - Letters2.zip1989 May 14 - 1992 Feb 24 (Folder 2)
      Personal correspondence.
  - inzip but should be Fax (sent).zip 1/3 Summer '97, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 35)